const level8questions = 
[
 
    {
        "question": "3 less than 389?",
        "options": ["136", "181", "190", "386"],
        "answer": "386"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 618?",
        "options": ["106", "516", "615", "540"],
        "answer": "615"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 923?",
        "options": ["920", "344", "229", "95"],
        "answer": "920"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 912?",
        "options": ["909", "752", "309", "78"],
        "answer": "909"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 873?",
        "options": ["596", "870", "157", "375"],
        "answer": "870"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 801?",
        "options": ["728", "798", "884", "128"],
        "answer": "798"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 627?",
        "options": ["674", "883", "494", "624"],
        "answer": "624"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 397?",
        "options": ["388", "964", "394", "797"],
        "answer": "394"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 915?",
        "options": ["912", "577", "649", "641"],
        "answer": "912"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 606?",
        "options": ["328", "837", "855", "603"],
        "answer": "603"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 432?",
        "options": ["210", "219", "50", "429"],
        "answer": "429"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 869?",
        "options": ["457", "388", "709", "866"],
        "answer": "866"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 792?",
        "options": ["476", "741", "239", "789"],
        "answer": "789"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 691?",
        "options": ["688", "441", "794", "44"],
        "answer": "688"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 297?",
        "options": ["294", "856", "265", "245"],
        "answer": "294"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 583?",
        "options": ["906", "644", "580", "213"],
        "answer": "580"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 706?",
        "options": ["520", "210", "703", "131"],
        "answer": "703"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 779?",
        "options": ["776", "764", "166", "519"],
        "answer": "776"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 352?",
        "options": ["330", "924", "606", "349"],
        "answer": "349"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 417?",
        "options": ["414", "791", "445", "559"],
        "answer": "414"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 761?",
        "options": ["394", "758", "738", "982"],
        "answer": "758"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 254?",
        "options": ["251", "682", "821", "215"],
        "answer": "251"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 217?",
        "options": ["913", "851", "799", "214"],
        "answer": "214"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 801?",
        "options": ["91", "798", "732", "399"],
        "answer": "798"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 896?",
        "options": ["248", "425", "893", "434"],
        "answer": "893"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 less than 391?",
        "options": ["976", "880", "388", "86"],
        "answer": "388"
      },
    {
        question: "3 less than 850?",
        options: ["672", "449", "847", "923"],
        answer: "847",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 442?",
        options: ["24", "439", "810", "307"],
        answer: "439",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 871?",
        options: ["946", "307", "868", "317"],
        answer: "868",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 34?",
        options: ["371", "31", "389", "982"],
        answer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 965?",
        options: ["727", "962", "926", "791"],
        answer: "962",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 84?",
        options: ["81", "265", "675", "973"],
        answer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 615?",
        options: ["612", "116", "834", "412"],
        answer: "612",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 294?",
        options: ["616", "128", "712", "291"],
        answer: "291",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 532?",
        options: ["817", "28", "182", "529"],
        answer: "529",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 381?",
        options: ["987", "452", "378", "735"],
        answer: "378",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 662?",
        options: ["386", "141", "862", "659"],
        answer: "659",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 275?",
        options: ["691", "501", "272", "630"],
        answer: "272",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 834?",
        options: ["584", "228", "831", "445"],
        answer: "831",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 43?",
        options: ["436", "40", "284", "733"],
        answer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 488?",
        options: ["65", "787", "485", "679"],
        answer: "485",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 625?",
        options: ["913", "909", "622", "503"],
        answer: "622",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 320?",
        options: ["96", "668", "317", "23"],
        answer: "317",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 908?",
        options: ["281", "132", "905", "334"],
        answer: "905",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 896?",
        options: ["600", "793", "646", "893"],
        answer: "893",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 57?",
        options: ["524", "54", "709", "855"],
        answer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 856?",
        options: ["853", "352", "188", "414"],
        answer: "853",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 606?",
        options: ["603", "840", "940", "974"],
        answer: "603",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 617?",
        options: ["916", "614", "414", "535"],
        answer: "614",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 683?",
        options: ["992", "818", "680", "125"],
        answer: "680",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 180?",
        options: ["329", "177", "397", "791"],
        answer: "177",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 11?",
        options: ["414", "214", "190", "8"],
        answer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 402?",
        options: ["499", "292", "565", "399"],
        answer: "399",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 195?",
        options: ["882", "883", "192", "572"],
        answer: "192",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 497?",
        options: ["456", "764", "223", "494"],
        answer: "494",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 264?",
        options: ["261", "962", "300", "165"],
        answer: "261",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 446?",
        options: ["443", "171", "684", "646"],
        answer: "443",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 327?",
        options: ["897", "324", "132", "327"],
        answer: "324",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 677?",
        options: ["285", "93", "174", "674"],
        answer: "674",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 890?",
        options: ["887", "770", "965", "118"],
        answer: "887",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 622?",
        options: ["619", "224", "824", "949"],
        answer: "619",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 552?",
        options: ["549", "442", "524", "669"],
        answer: "549",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 7?",
        options: ["576", "178", "4", "532"],
        answer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 666?",
        options: ["266", "251", "663", "180"],
        answer: "663",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 540?",
        options: ["374", "190", "991", "537"],
        answer: "537",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 347?",
        options: ["545", "149", "344", "647"],
        answer: "344",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 395?",
        options: ["392", "688", "630", "439"],
        answer: "392",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 539?",
        options: ["536", "136", "793", "818"],
        answer: "536",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 31?",
        options: ["353", "28", "298", "748"],
        answer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 871?",
        options: ["868", "49", "101", "349"],
        answer: "868",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 860?",
        options: ["937", "995", "439", "857"],
        answer: "857",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 49?",
        options: ["192", "862", "847", "46"],
        answer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 917?",
        options: ["465", "652", "654", "914"],
        answer: "914",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 362?",
        options: ["297", "988", "149", "359"],
        answer: "359",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 63?",
        options: ["369", "843", "60", "663"],
        answer: "60",
    },
    
    {
        question: "3 less than 725?",
        options: ["313", "3", "722", "797"],
        answer: "722",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 954?",
        options: ["474", "701", "951", "223"],
        answer: "951",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 901?",
        options: ["545", "242", "898", "17"],
        answer: "898",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 217?",
        options: ["504", "789", "214", "925"],
        answer: "214",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 72?",
        options: ["69", "377", "690", "353"],
        answer: "69",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 742?",
        options: ["794", "339", "739", "122"],
        answer: "739",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 443?",
        options: ["195", "440", "861", "62"],
        answer: "440",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 794?",
        options: ["791", "912", "439", "807"],
        answer: "791",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 649?",
        options: ["386", "459", "92", "646"],
        answer: "646",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 317?",
        options: ["778", "437", "311", "314"],
        answer: "314",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 637?",
        options: ["929", "514", "445", "634"],
        answer: "634",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 864?",
        options: ["861", "965", "866", "717"],
        answer: "861",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 434?",
        options: ["431", "562", "427", "326"],
        answer: "431",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 207?",
        options: ["204", "604", "101", "774"],
        answer: "204",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 314?",
        options: ["28", "311", "126", "663"],
        answer: "311",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 921?",
        options: ["188", "918", "340", "298"],
        answer: "918",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 507?",
        options: ["858", "541", "504", "325"],
        answer: "504",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 963?",
        options: ["48", "960", "282", "758"],
        answer: "960",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 48?",
        options: ["45", "608", "288", "285"],
        answer: "45",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 774?",
        options: ["771", "496", "577", "651"],
        answer: "771",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 626?",
        options: ["866", "699", "623", "621"],
        answer: "623",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 899?",
        options: ["936", "387", "896", "220"],
        answer: "896",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 40?",
        options: ["37", "208", "137", "404"],
        answer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 957?",
        options: ["586", "954", "131", "502"],
        answer: "954",
    },
    {
        question: "3 less than 829?",
        options: ["504", "826", "760", "490"],
        answer: "826",
    },
    
    {
        question: "4 less than 652?",
        options: ["48", "608", "557", "648"],
        answer: "648",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 653?",
        options: ["649", "124", "957", "926"],
        answer: "649",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 809?",
        options: ["947", "549", "909", "805"],
        answer: "805",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 804?",
        options: ["106", "405", "911", "800"],
        answer: "800",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 879?",
        options: ["875", "440", "164", "732"],
        answer: "875",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 196?",
        options: ["473", "192", "10", "399"],
        answer: "192",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 489?",
        options: ["328", "409", "709", "485"],
        answer: "485",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 110?",
        options: ["106", "874", "740", "821"],
        answer: "106",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 541?",
        options: ["537", "235", "293", "654"],
        answer: "537",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 343?",
        options: ["528", "453", "339", "63"],
        answer: "339",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 803?",
        options: ["664", "799", "890", "391"],
        answer: "799",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 383?",
        options: ["664", "450", "379", "125"],
        answer: "379",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 271?",
        options: ["197", "454", "267", "599"],
        answer: "267",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 410?",
        options: ["406", "488", "32", "893"],
        answer: "406",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 712?",
        options: ["608", "257", "708", "605"],
        answer: "708",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 391?",
        options: ["387", "632", "778", "191"],
        answer: "387",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 319?",
        options: ["457", "372", "315", "268"],
        answer: "315",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 482?",
        options: ["96", "370", "478", "612"],
        answer: "478",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 272?",
        options: ["268", "882", "139", "245"],
        answer: "268",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 39?",
        options: ["632", "35", "802", "619"],
        answer: "35",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 917?",
        options: ["586", "829", "913", "894"],
        answer: "913",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 188?",
        options: ["354", "184", "203", "967"],
        answer: "184",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 341?",
        options: ["960", "257", "162", "337"],
        answer: "337",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 694?",
        options: ["690", "717", "494", "319"],
        answer: "690",
    },
    {
        question: "4 less than 984?",
        options: ["827", "534", "980", "631"],
        answer: "980",
    },
    
     
    {
        question: "7 less than 917?",
        options: ["608", "882", "212", "910"],
        answer: "910"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 555?",
        options: ["673", "573", "548", "685"],
        answer: "548"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 782?",
        options: ["484", "685", "775", "326"],
        answer: "775"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 670?",
        options: ["663", "905", "261", "189"],
        answer: "663"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 187?",
        options: ["898", "180", "940", "462"],
        answer: "180"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 649?",
        options: ["642", "18", "773", "654"],
        answer: "642"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 720?",
        options: ["926", "713", "11", "702"],
        answer: "713"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 515?",
        options: ["176", "730", "653", "508"],
        answer: "508"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 793?",
        options: ["875", "292", "786", "621"],
        answer: "786"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 319?",
        options: ["273", "938", "67", "312"],
        answer: "312"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 209?",
        options: ["866", "979", "202", "757"],
        answer: "202"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 432?",
        options: ["306", "810", "425", "631"],
        answer: "425"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 635?",
        options: ["628", "257", "572", "734"],
        answer: "628"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 463?",
        options: ["435", "667", "381", "456"],
        answer: "456"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 164?",
        options: ["157", "873", "530", "342"],
        answer: "157"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 374?",
        options: ["367", "96", "130", "278"],
        answer: "367"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 499?",
        options: ["160", "963", "702", "492"],
        answer: "492"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 457?",
        options: ["960", "450", "518", "263"],
        answer: "450"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 780?",
        options: ["773", "281", "684", "917"],
        answer: "773"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 703?",
        options: ["984", "696", "372", "647"],
        answer: "696"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 362?",
        options: ["355", "34", "884", "71"],
        answer: "355"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 973?",
        options: ["563", "316", "167", "966"],
        answer: "966"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 460?",
        options: ["952", "453", "915", "573"],
        answer: "453"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 417?",
        options: ["224", "410", "476", "807"],
        answer: "410"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 968?",
        options: ["877", "604", "961", "517"],
        answer: "961"
      },
      
      {
        question: "7 less than 503?",
        options: ["496", "371", "125", "451"],
        answer: "496"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 150?",
        options: ["816", "48", "143", "164"],
        answer: "143"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 984?",
        options: ["322", "973", "977", "542"],
        answer: "977"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 727?",
        options: ["739", "747", "495", "720"],
        answer: "720"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 439?",
        options: ["244", "432", "813", "494"],
        answer: "432"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 899?",
        options: ["88", "892", "353", "941"],
        answer: "892"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 754?",
        options: ["826", "747", "925", "974"],
        answer: "747"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 499?",
        options: ["697", "492", "122", "810"],
        answer: "492"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 329?",
        options: ["562", "739", "322", "910"],
        answer: "322"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 427?",
        options: ["199", "420", "276", "967"],
        answer: "420"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 246?",
        options: ["280", "239", "469", "542"],
        answer: "239"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 666?",
        options: ["659", "107", "891", "948"],
        answer: "659"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 314?",
        options: ["452", "307", "94", "351"],
        answer: "307"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 595?",
        options: ["113", "436", "405", "588"],
        answer: "588"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 261?",
        options: ["254", "106", "891", "356"],
        answer: "254"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 441?",
        options: ["923", "253", "434", "430"],
        answer: "434"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 943?",
        options: ["208", "849", "936", "478"],
        answer: "936"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 572?",
        options: ["283", "954", "147", "565"],
        answer: "565"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 933?",
        options: ["663", "500", "495", "926"],
        answer: "926"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 565?",
        options: ["313", "812", "510", "558"],
        answer: "558"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 492?",
        options: ["485", "927", "869", "903"],
        answer: "485"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 38?",
        options: ["882", "31", "165", "670"],
        answer: "31"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 14?",
        options: ["7", "796", "582", "527"],
        answer: "7"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 654?",
        options: ["985", "771", "647", "663"],
        answer: "647"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 33?",
        options: ["25", "26", "346", "485"],
        answer: "26"
      },
      
      {
        question: "7 less than 802?",
        options: ["858", "331", "156", "795"],
        answer: "795"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 749?",
        options: ["742", "557", "468", "485"],
        answer: "742"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 148?",
        options: ["225", "141", "901", "439"],
        answer: "141"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 101?",
        options: ["36", "246", "94", "679"],
        answer: "94"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 131?",
        options: ["334", "38", "511", "124"],
        answer: "124"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 824?",
        options: ["817", "897", "122", "539"],
        answer: "817"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 393?",
        options: ["232", "394", "950", "386"],
        answer: "386"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 66?",
        options: ["59", "266", "635", "340"],
        answer: "59"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 314?",
        options: ["408", "284", "307", "933"],
        answer: "307"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 96?",
        options: ["408", "545", "740", "89"],
        answer: "89"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 235?",
        options: ["228", "272", "668", "669"],
        answer: "228"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 711?",
        options: ["857", "854", "704", "391"],
        answer: "704"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 551?",
        options: ["433", "570", "903", "544"],
        answer: "544"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 524?",
        options: ["12", "828", "517", "343"],
        answer: "517"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 938?",
        options: ["81", "931", "197", "509"],
        answer: "931"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 176?",
        options: ["789", "169", "86", "647"],
        answer: "169"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 631?",
        options: ["104", "624", "859", "502"],
        answer: "624"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 266?",
        options: ["968", "259", "275", "718"],
        answer: "259"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 860?",
        options: ["913", "853", "427", "940"],
        answer: "853"
      },
      {
        question: "7 less than 353?",
        options: ["170", "963", "285", "346"],
        answer: "346"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 23?",
        "options": ["938", "19", "507", "733"],
        "answer": "19"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 732?",
        "options": ["975", "728", "366", "303"],
        "answer": "728"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 200?",
        "options": ["594", "196", "379", "187"],
        "answer": "196"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 19?",
        "options": ["872", "15", "89", "318"],
        "answer": "15"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 452?",
        "options": ["207", "973", "448", "951"],
        "answer": "448"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 439?",
        "options": ["435", "712", "898", "718"],
        "answer": "435"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 574?",
        "options": ["258", "652", "286", "570"],
        "answer": "570"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 869?",
        "options": ["24", "133", "207", "865"],
        "answer": "865"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 567?",
        "options": ["563", "280", "506", "963"],
        "answer": "563"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 474?",
        "options": ["470", "154", "843", "460"],
        "answer": "470"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 332?",
        "options": ["146", "203", "328", "78"],
        "answer": "328"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 721?",
        "options": ["717", "729", "323", "647"],
        "answer": "717"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 271?",
        "options": ["408", "267", "610", "715"],
        "answer": "267"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 817?",
        "options": ["248", "813", "844", "317"],
        "answer": "813"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 888?",
        "options": ["144", "632", "884", "957"],
        "answer": "884"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 864?",
        "options": ["809", "763", "213", "860"],
        "answer": "860"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 970?",
        "options": ["776", "571", "966", "772"],
        "answer": "966"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 205?",
        "options": ["16", "529", "439", "201"],
        "answer": "201"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 649?",
        "options": ["12", "645", "230", "852"],
        "answer": "645"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 168?",
        "options": ["164", "132", "675", "708"],
        "answer": "164"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 698?",
        "options": ["435", "156", "694", "84"],
        "answer": "694"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 151?",
        "options": ["400", "444", "147", "20"],
        "answer": "147"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 113?",
        "options": ["920", "322", "77", "109"],
        "answer": "109"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 635?",
        "options": ["690", "274", "923", "631"],
        "answer": "631"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 797?",
        "options": ["793", "273", "123", "617"],
        "answer": "793"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "4 less than 19?",
        "options": ["15", "97", "275", "69"],
        "answer": "15"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 709?",
        "options": ["393", "705", "243", "332"],
        "answer": "705"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 523?",
        "options": ["519", "188", "316", "749"],
        "answer": "519"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 354?",
        "options": ["350", "49", "699", "527"],
        "answer": "350"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 690?",
        "options": ["172", "686", "677", "685"],
        "answer": "686"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 943?",
        "options": ["501", "892", "939", "237"],
        "answer": "939"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 756?",
        "options": ["752", "140", "5", "487"],
        "answer": "752"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 526?",
        "options": ["97", "874", "522", "420"],
        "answer": "522"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 532?",
        "options": ["728", "528", "508", "575"],
        "answer": "528"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 861?",
        "options": ["536", "706", "857", "141"],
        "answer": "857"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 255?",
        "options": ["643", "251", "556", "533"],
        "answer": "251"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 928?",
        "options": ["160", "346", "767", "924"],
        "answer": "924"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 676?",
        "options": ["672", "720", "637", "333"],
        "answer": "672"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 308?",
        "options": ["304", "736", "427", "246"],
        "answer": "304"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 134?",
        "options": ["130", "432", "545", "932"],
        "answer": "130"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 930?",
        "options": ["719", "926", "204", "319"],
        "answer": "926"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 178?",
        "options": ["830", "474", "174", "6"],
        "answer": "174"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 277?",
        "options": ["602", "273", "131", "503"],
        "answer": "273"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 831?",
        "options": ["553", "706", "827", "533"],
        "answer": "827"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 399?",
        "options": ["395", "428", "893", "118"],
        "answer": "395"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 335?",
        "options": ["331", "696", "353", "388"],
        "answer": "331"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 323?",
        "options": ["319", "882", "652", "789"],
        "answer": "319"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 333?",
        "options": ["785", "329", "394", "190"],
        "answer": "329"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 105?",
        "options": ["792", "930", "101", "580"],
        "answer": "101"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 795?",
        "options": ["888", "12", "791", "574"],
        "answer": "791"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "4 less than 109?",
        "options": ["105", "386", "356", "421"],
        "answer": "105"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 31?",
        "options": ["27", "325", "868", "349"],
        "answer": "27"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 792?",
        "options": ["539", "883", "788", "68"],
        "answer": "788"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 434?",
        "options": ["160", "430", "555", "788"],
        "answer": "430"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 476?",
        "options": ["489", "472", "866", "519"],
        "answer": "472"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 722?",
        "options": ["33", "533", "825", "718"],
        "answer": "718"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 131?",
        "options": ["127", "619", "718", "375"],
        "answer": "127"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 981?",
        "options": ["8", "748", "405", "977"],
        "answer": "977"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 35?",
        "options": ["225", "869", "702", "31"],
        "answer": "31"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 284?",
        "options": ["321", "772", "597", "280"],
        "answer": "280"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 833?",
        "options": ["218", "354", "642", "829"],
        "answer": "829"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 338?",
        "options": ["336", "410", "509", "334"],
        "answer": "334"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 686?",
        "options": ["116", "764", "751", "682"],
        "answer": "682"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 663?",
        "options": ["675", "532", "213", "659"],
        "answer": "659"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 256?",
        "options": ["810", "108", "789", "252"],
        "answer": "252"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 392?",
        "options": ["929", "109", "388", "46"],
        "answer": "388"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 643?",
        "options": ["268", "350", "807", "639"],
        "answer": "639"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 123?",
        "options": ["912", "530", "119", "335"],
        "answer": "119"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 314?",
        "options": ["310", "655", "664", "663"],
        "answer": "310"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 900?",
        "options": ["276", "896", "957", "335"],
        "answer": "896"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 193?",
        "options": ["25", "106", "189", "429"],
        "answer": "189"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 334?",
        "options": ["680", "259", "330", "844"],
        "answer": "330"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 556?",
        "options": ["552", "426", "316", "671"],
        "answer": "552"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 159?",
        "options": ["916", "102", "359", "155"],
        "answer": "155"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 less than 606?",
        "options": ["602", "856", "701", "695"],
        "answer": "602"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "5 less than 438?",
        "options": ["426", "75", "433", "804"],
        "answer": "433"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 193?",
        "options": ["304", "188", "784", "600"],
        "answer": "188"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 646?",
        "options": ["835", "28", "548", "641"],
        "answer": "641"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 155?",
        "options": ["150", "809", "425", "253"],
        "answer": "150"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 934?",
        "options": ["929", "416", "741", "679"],
        "answer": "929"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 86?",
        "options": ["825", "81", "177", "923"],
        "answer": "81"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 816?",
        "options": ["296", "56", "811", "219"],
        "answer": "811"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 96?",
        "options": ["922", "380", "335", "91"],
        "answer": "91"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 989?",
        "options": ["786", "984", "820", "679"],
        "answer": "984"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 335?",
        "options": ["688", "413", "330", "102"],
        "answer": "330"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 617?",
        "options": ["716", "972", "895", "612"],
        "answer": "612"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 531?",
        "options": ["526", "806", "769", "406"],
        "answer": "526"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 76?",
        "options": ["106", "492", "130", "71"],
        "answer": "71"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 809?",
        "options": ["239", "157", "804", "23"],
        "answer": "804"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 800?",
        "options": ["795", "673", "682", "188"],
        "answer": "795"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 985?",
        "options": ["784", "954", "168", "980"],
        "answer": "980"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 989?",
        "options": ["25", "984", "149", "870"],
        "answer": "984"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 434?",
        "options": ["280", "377", "429", "229"],
        "answer": "429"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 604?",
        "options": ["33", "507", "677", "599"],
        "answer": "599"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 828?",
        "options": ["712", "504", "115", "823"],
        "answer": "823"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 716?",
        "options": ["896", "921", "188", "711"],
        "answer": "711"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 23?",
        "options": ["18", "232", "604", "422"],
        "answer": "18"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 283?",
        "options": ["278", "554", "660", "174"],
        "answer": "278"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 139?",
        "options": ["418", "858", "134", "935"],
        "answer": "134"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 375?",
        "options": ["852", "370", "287", "543"],
        "answer": "370"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 831?",
        "options": ["898", "826", "931", "15"],
        "answer": "826"
      },
    
        {
            "question": "5 less than 853?",
            "options": ["168", "257", "549", "848"],
            "answer": "848"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 956?",
            "options": ["844", "805", "951", "934"],
            "answer": "951"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 844?",
            "options": ["152", "839", "577", "965"],
            "answer": "839"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 443?",
            "options": ["817", "438", "907", "877"],
            "answer": "438"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 982?",
            "options": ["977", "378", "443", "958"],
            "answer": "977"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 229?",
            "options": ["914", "926", "224", "471"],
            "answer": "224"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 871?",
            "options": ["296", "866", "98", "88"],
            "answer": "866"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 767?",
            "options": ["762", "64", "652", "791"],
            "answer": "762"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 291?",
            "options": ["635", "286", "141", "430"],
            "answer": "286"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 907?",
            "options": ["416", "902", "569", "51"],
            "answer": "902"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 352?",
            "options": ["353", "347", "299", "827"],
            "answer": "347"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 476?",
            "options": ["471", "626", "99", "470"],
            "answer": "471"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 55?",
            "options": ["846", "673", "534", "50"],
            "answer": "50"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 902?",
            "options": ["897", "251", "13", "527"],
            "answer": "897"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 882?",
            "options": ["856", "877", "675", "445"],
            "answer": "877"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 797?",
            "options": ["792", "848", "577", "959"],
            "answer": "792"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 711?",
            "options": ["706", "929", "810", "219"],
            "answer": "706"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 475?",
            "options": ["480", "470", "569", "287"],
            "answer": "470"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 426?",
            "options": ["202", "92", "557", "421"],
            "answer": "421"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 889?",
            "options": ["177", "947", "980", "884"],
            "answer": "884"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 965?",
            "options": ["164", "960", "765", "302"],
            "answer": "960"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 735?",
            "options": ["873", "83", "556", "730"],
            "answer": "730"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 917?",
            "options": ["779", "789", "439", "912"],
            "answer": "912"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 231?",
            "options": ["226", "145", "795", "756"],
            "answer": "226"
        },
    
     {
            "question": "5 less than 82?",
            "options": ["77", "249", "905", "255"],
            "answer": "77"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 639?",
            "options": ["634", "233", "829", "870"],
            "answer": "634"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 857?",
            "options": ["714", "797", "898", "852"],
            "answer": "852"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 855?",
            "options": ["850", "953", "956", "60"],
            "answer": "850"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 889?",
            "options": ["636", "914", "884", "244"],
            "answer": "884"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 140?",
            "options": ["697", "310", "135", "967"],
            "answer": "135"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 508?",
            "options": ["752", "153", "503", "78"],
            "answer": "503"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 904?",
            "options": ["899", "738", "700", "391"],
            "answer": "899"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 656?",
            "options": ["969", "702", "651", "814"],
            "answer": "651"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 953?",
            "options": ["921", "948", "722", "76"],
            "answer": "948"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 250?",
            "options": ["820", "862", "245", "567"],
            "answer": "245"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 137?",
            "options": ["858", "851", "132", "342"],
            "answer": "132"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 603?",
            "options": ["598", "124", "589", "247"],
            "answer": "598"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 826?",
            "options": ["497", "981", "821", "703"],
            "answer": "821"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 919?",
            "options": ["808", "129", "766", "914"],
            "answer": "914"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 235?",
            "options": ["35", "486", "183", "230"],
            "answer": "230"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 641?",
            "options": ["636", "819", "646", "919"],
            "answer": "636"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 68?",
            "options": ["41", "581", "63", "198"],
            "answer": "63"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 507?",
            "options": ["502", "393", "834", "220"],
            "answer": "502"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 397?",
            "options": ["139", "79", "392", "183"],
            "answer": "392"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 888?",
            "options": ["100", "165", "883", "182"],
            "answer": "883"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 446?",
            "options": ["744", "689", "441", "538"],
            "answer": "441"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 535?",
            "options": ["828", "530", "950", "231"],
            "answer": "530"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 221?",
            "options": ["897", "883", "216", "100"],
            "answer": "216"
        },
        {
            "question": "5 less than 994?",
            "options": ["442", "597", "326", "989"],
            "answer": "989"
        },
    
      {
        "question": "5 less than 511?",
        "options": ["506", "620", "782", "647"],
        "answer": "506"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 862?",
        "options": ["857", "784", "526", "928"],
        "answer": "857"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 844?",
        "options": ["108", "839", "236", "542"],
        "answer": "839"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 51?",
        "options": ["649", "19", "190", "46"],
        "answer": "46"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 462?",
        "options": ["768", "840", "457", "52"],
        "answer": "457"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 6?",
        "options": ["1", "88", "187", "31"],
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 800?",
        "options": ["608", "795", "977", "63"],
        "answer": "795"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 632?",
        "options": ["627", "515", "980", "84"],
        "answer": "627"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 762?",
        "options": ["448", "808", "757", "45"],
        "answer": "757"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 104?",
        "options": ["748", "119", "99", "959"],
        "answer": "99"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 19?",
        "options": ["936", "188", "14", "526"],
        "answer": "14"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 921?",
        "options": ["916", "787", "820", "947"],
        "answer": "916"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 572?",
        "options": ["567", "168", "258", "91"],
        "answer": "567"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 682?",
        "options": ["253", "677", "502", "791"],
        "answer": "677"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 988?",
        "options": ["983", "257", "235", "335"],
        "answer": "983"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 791?",
        "options": ["786", "954", "770", "358"],
        "answer": "786"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 437?",
        "options": ["728", "949", "432", "278"],
        "answer": "432"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 535?",
        "options": ["193", "378", "429", "530"],
        "answer": "530"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 800?",
        "options": ["529", "706", "795", "26"],
        "answer": "795"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 266?",
        "options": ["336", "489", "261", "164"],
        "answer": "261"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 871?",
        "options": ["256", "866", "707", "47"],
        "answer": "866"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 534?",
        "options": ["370", "828", "529", "247"],
        "answer": "529"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 148?",
        "options": ["143", "617", "937", "509"],
        "answer": "143"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 778?",
        "options": ["773", "489", "836", "927"],
        "answer": "773"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 less than 825?",
        "options": ["461", "820", "54", "103"],
        "answer": "820"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "5 less than 825?",
        "options": ["461", "820", "54", "103"],
        "answer": "820"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 734?",
        "options": ["663", "728", "643", "671"],
        "answer": "728"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 380?",
        "options": ["192", "376", "302", "374"],
        "answer": "374"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 322?",
        "options": ["309", "316", "149", "534"],
        "answer": "316"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 674?",
        "options": ["185", "668", "603", "967"],
        "answer": "668"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 84?",
        "options": ["162", "228", "658", "78"],
        "answer": "78"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 577?",
        "options": ["267", "571", "67", "563"],
        "answer": "571"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 620?",
        "options": ["337", "614", "22", "31"],
        "answer": "614"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 378?",
        "options": ["793", "499", "372", "437"],
        "answer": "372"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 809?",
        "options": ["787", "932", "837", "803"],
        "answer": "803"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 770?",
        "options": ["764", "457", "355", "900"],
        "answer": "764"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 891?",
        "options": ["993", "885", "878", "47"],
        "answer": "885"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 413?",
        "options": ["728", "826", "407", "44"],
        "answer": "407"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 62?",
        "options": ["267", "383", "807", "56"],
        "answer": "56"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 956?",
        "options": ["684", "990", "950", "551"],
        "answer": "950"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 713?",
        "options": ["656", "707", "225", "500"],
        "answer": "707"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 269?",
        "options": ["817", "263", "277", "750"],
        "answer": "263"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 281?",
        "options": ["275", "618", "772", "142"],
        "answer": "275"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 148?",
        "options": ["142", "934", "22", "238"],
        "answer": "142"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 573?",
        "options": ["440", "567", "797", "919"],
        "answer": "567"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 920?",
        "options": ["529", "914", "883", "807"],
        "answer": "914"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 185?",
        "options": ["82", "543", "130", "179"],
        "answer": "179"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 918?",
        "options": ["530", "18", "912", "462"],
        "answer": "912"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 50?",
        "options": ["834", "44", "835", "748"],
        "answer": "44"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 165?",
        "options": ["159", "978", "290", "5"],
        "answer": "159"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 991?",
        "options": ["785", "985", "146", "547"],
        "answer": "985"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "6 less than 310?",
        "options": ["282", "304", "108", "917"],
        "answer": "304"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 394?",
        "options": ["388", "935", "292", "807"],
        "answer": "388"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 835?",
        "options": ["829", "168", "322", "732"],
        "answer": "829"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 80?",
        "options": ["176", "186", "150", "74"],
        "answer": "74"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 878?",
        "options": ["442", "872", "761", "738"],
        "answer": "872"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 227?",
        "options": ["436", "221", "973", "895"],
        "answer": "221"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 784?",
        "options": ["169", "251", "778", "430"],
        "answer": "778"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 120?",
        "options": ["739", "411", "114", "478"],
        "answer": "114"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 16?",
        "options": ["45", "293", "182", "10"],
        "answer": "10"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 653?",
        "options": ["968", "647", "138", "514"],
        "answer": "647"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 904?",
        "options": ["186", "19", "898", "646"],
        "answer": "898"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 375?",
        "options": ["360", "540", "982", "369"],
        "answer": "369"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 651?",
        "options": ["435", "949", "303", "645"],
        "answer": "645"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 52?",
        "options": ["624", "961", "46", "48"],
        "answer": "46"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 106?",
        "options": ["713", "722", "100", "603"],
        "answer": "100"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 886?",
        "options": ["968", "480", "880", "811"],
        "answer": "880"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 958?",
        "options": ["200", "468", "349", "952"],
        "answer": "952"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 119?",
        "options": ["113", "489", "554", "810"],
        "answer": "113"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 521?",
        "options": ["210", "947", "515", "92"],
        "answer": "515"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 451?",
        "options": ["445", "885", "396", "645"],
        "answer": "445"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 68?",
        "options": ["386", "524", "796", "62"],
        "answer": "62"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 425?",
        "options": ["320", "948", "853", "419"],
        "answer": "419"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 764?",
        "options": ["758", "368", "443", "734"],
        "answer": "758"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 160?",
        "options": ["154", "760", "2", "972"],
        "answer": "154"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 872?",
        "options": ["466", "242", "866", "387"],
        "answer": "866"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "6 less than 423?",
        "options": ["602", "343", "503", "417"],
        "answer": "417"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 903?",
        "options": ["360", "897", "260", "84"],
        "answer": "897"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 292?",
        "options": ["286", "865", "324", "622"],
        "answer": "286"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 243?",
        "options": ["237", "32", "868", "456"],
        "answer": "237"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 999?",
        "options": ["800", "152", "326", "993"],
        "answer": "993"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 223?",
        "options": ["713", "715", "217", "308"],
        "answer": "217"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 254?",
        "options": ["248", "465", "291", "705"],
        "answer": "248"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 434?",
        "options": ["581", "500", "428", "469"],
        "answer": "428"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 870?",
        "options": ["393", "498", "517", "864"],
        "answer": "864"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 855?",
        "options": ["817", "890", "849", "933"],
        "answer": "849"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 108?",
        "options": ["102", "132", "885", "750"],
        "answer": "102"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 177?",
        "options": ["626", "611", "171", "151"],
        "answer": "171"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 586?",
        "options": ["554", "276", "292", "580"],
        "answer": "580"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 219?",
        "options": ["213", "178", "93", "311"],
        "answer": "213"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 192?",
        "options": ["480", "186", "425", "577"],
        "answer": "186"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 76?",
        "options": ["811", "70", "925", "503"],
        "answer": "70"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 251?",
        "options": ["241", "405", "245", "310"],
        "answer": "245"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 537?",
        "options": ["531", "920", "91", "916"],
        "answer": "531"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 365?",
        "options": ["98", "852", "359", "350"],
        "answer": "359"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 27?",
        "options": ["833", "977", "733", "21"],
        "answer": "21"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 711?",
        "options": ["705", "180", "436", "935"],
        "answer": "705"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 805?",
        "options": ["799", "64", "785", "723"],
        "answer": "799"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 516?",
        "options": ["873", "515", "510", "519"],
        "answer": "510"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 841?",
        "options": ["835", "506", "100", "237"],
        "answer": "835"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 less than 227?",
        "options": ["221", "530", "652", "358"],
        "answer": "221"
      },
    
        {
            "question": "6 less than 342?",
            "options": ["336", "697", "170", "283"],
            "answer": "336"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 79?",
            "options": ["258", "73", "578", "62"],
            "answer": "73"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 54?",
            "options": ["768", "48", "209", "490"],
            "answer": "48"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 80?",
            "options": ["352", "611", "74", "871"],
            "answer": "74"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 141?",
            "options": ["126", "135", "915", "782"],
            "answer": "135"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 497?",
            "options": ["625", "68", "491", "270"],
            "answer": "491"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 238?",
            "options": ["232", "336", "306", "822"],
            "answer": "232"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 934?",
            "options": ["192", "928", "389", "382"],
            "answer": "928"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 372?",
            "options": ["120", "162", "703", "366"],
            "answer": "366"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 793?",
            "options": ["32", "787", "154", "270"],
            "answer": "787"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 834?",
            "options": ["432", "232", "828", "261"],
            "answer": "828"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 84?",
            "options": ["353", "78", "166", "815"],
            "answer": "78"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 719?",
            "options": ["353", "42", "713", "537"],
            "answer": "713"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 517?",
            "options": ["75", "884", "511", "917"],
            "answer": "511"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 730?",
            "options": ["849", "724", "21", "503"],
            "answer": "724"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 120?",
            "options": ["347", "114", "477", "726"],
            "answer": "114"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 983?",
            "options": ["832", "834", "977", "632"],
            "answer": "977"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 686?",
            "options": ["729", "680", "788", "902"],
            "answer": "680"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 167?",
            "options": ["90", "250", "861", "161"],
            "answer": "161"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 44?",
            "options": ["913", "613", "366", "38"],
            "answer": "38"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 961?",
            "options": ["153", "796", "955", "463"],
            "answer": "955"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 352?",
            "options": ["48", "346", "169", "179"],
            "answer": "346"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 292?",
            "options": ["286", "944", "229", "93"],
            "answer": "286"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 347?",
            "options": ["341", "456", "808", "424"],
            "answer": "341"
        },
        {
            "question": "6 less than 825?",
            "options": ["819", "881", "649", "662"],
            "answer": "819"
        },

    {
      "question": "7 less than 424?",
      "options": ["417", "453", "863", "31"],
      "answer": "417"
    },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 598?",
        "options": ["591", "591", "591", "591"],
        "answer": "591"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 816?",
        "options": ["809", "256", "612", "253"],
        "answer": "809"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 722?",
        "options": ["472", "114", "740", "715"],
        "answer": "715"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 304?",
        "options": ["969", "948", "789", "297"],
        "answer": "297"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 411?",
        "options": ["24", "282", "917", "404"],
        "answer": "404"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 727?",
        "options": ["451", "556", "720", "245"],
        "answer": "720"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 312?",
        "options": ["323", "305", "67", "796"],
        "answer": "305"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 224?",
        "options": ["169", "62", "217", "631"],
        "answer": "217"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 891?",
        "options": ["985", "884", "730", "451"],
        "answer": "884"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 201?",
        "options": ["842", "194", "36", "799"],
        "answer": "194"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 366?",
        "options": ["329", "781", "359", "590"],
        "answer": "359"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 774?",
        "options": ["767", "256", "10", "982"],
        "answer": "767"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 963?",
        "options": ["584", "956", "395", "605"],
        "answer": "956"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 362?",
        "options": ["912", "548", "355", "79"],
        "answer": "355"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 819?",
        "options": ["424", "812", "562", "333"],
        "answer": "812"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 667?",
        "options": ["660", "561", "426", "754"],
        "answer": "660"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 19?",
        "options": ["666", "12", "220", "925"],
        "answer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 920?",
        "options": ["913", "37", "492", "613"],
        "answer": "913"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 767?",
        "options": ["760", "729", "906", "742"],
        "answer": "760"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "7 less than 707?",
        "options": ["224", "564", "700", "821"],
        "answer": "700"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 47?",
        "options": ["40", "146", "750", "175"],
        "answer": "40"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 755?",
        "options": ["688", "748", "782", "975"],
        "answer": "748"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 100?",
        "options": ["513", "93", "347", "171"],
        "answer": "93"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 761?",
        "options": ["468", "754", "958", "102"],
        "answer": "754"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 462?",
        "options": ["284", "455", "133", "118"],
        "answer": "455"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 618?",
        "options": ["88", "611", "612", "726"],
        "answer": "611"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 294?",
        "options": ["355", "68", "287", "671"],
        "answer": "287"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 332?",
        "options": ["808", "401", "325", "526"],
        "answer": "325"
      },
      {
        "question": "7 less than 961?",
        "options": ["568", "954", "281", "59"],
        "answer": "954"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 740?",
        "options": ["425", "732", "27", "745"],
        "answer": "732"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 260?",
        "options": ["235", "252", "726", "558"],
        "answer": "252"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 89?",
        "options": ["144", "81", "929", "595"],
        "answer": "81"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 704?",
        "options": ["696", "616", "539", "548"],
        "answer": "696"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 25?",
        "options": ["733", "17", "405", "390"],
        "answer": "17"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 232?",
        "options": ["3", "716", "224", "495"],
        "answer": "224"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 445?",
        "options": ["437", "642", "979", "365"],
        "answer": "437"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 734?",
        "options": ["36", "726", "341", "292"],
        "answer": "726"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 525?",
        "options": ["347", "508", "517", "461"],
        "answer": "517"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 60?",
        "options": ["52", "979", "333", "982"],
        "answer": "52"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 308?",
        "options": ["648", "896", "300", "200"],
        "answer": "300"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 448?",
        "options": ["475", "900", "440", "389"],
        "answer": "440"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 718?",
        "options": ["563", "710", "292", "397"],
        "answer": "710"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 304?",
        "options": ["70", "908", "182", "296"],
        "answer": "296"
      },
      {
        "question": "8 less than 710?",
        "options": ["408", "452", "975", "702"],
        "answer": "702"
      },
    
        {
            "question": "8 less than 371?",
            "options": ["475", "229", "142", "363"],
            "answer": "363"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 173?",
            "options": ["112", "557", "583", "165"],
            "answer": "165"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 427?",
            "options": ["419", "743", "774", "527"],
            "answer": "419"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 542?",
            "options": ["534", "426", "563", "397"],
            "answer": "534"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 78?",
            "options": ["617", "517", "599", "70"],
            "answer": "70"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 53?",
            "options": ["593", "121", "802", "45"],
            "answer": "45"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 437?",
            "options": ["841", "20", "429", "542"],
            "answer": "429"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 893?",
            "options": ["248", "356", "885", "104"],
            "answer": "885"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 656?",
            "options": ["938", "242", "660", "648"],
            "answer": "648"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 301?",
            "options": ["577", "262", "293", "582"],
            "answer": "293"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 96?",
            "options": ["816", "88", "465", "113"],
            "answer": "88"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 148?",
            "options": ["434", "140", "10", "882"],
            "answer": "140"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 811?",
            "options": ["274", "803", "845", "349"],
            "answer": "803"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 391?",
            "options": ["88", "225", "124", "383"],
            "answer": "383"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 919?",
            "options": ["320", "911", "518", "79"],
            "answer": "911"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 589?",
            "options": ["581", "408", "33", "850"],
            "answer": "581"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 402?",
            "options": ["810", "973", "394", "878"],
            "answer": "394"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 810?",
            "options": ["802", "176", "395", "709"],
            "answer": "802"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 65?",
            "options": ["455", "63", "735", "57"],
            "answer": "57"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 531?",
            "options": ["58", "796", "523", "526"],
            "answer": "523"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 501?",
            "options": ["868", "452", "493", "231"],
            "answer": "493"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 97?",
            "options": ["952", "929", "89", "825"],
            "answer": "89"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 716?",
            "options": ["401", "708", "389", "118"],
            "answer": "708"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 411?",
            "options": ["403", "736", "347", "392"],
            "answer": "403"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 76?",
            "options": ["83", "68", "333", "519"],
            "answer": "68"
        },
    
        {
            "question": "8 less than 963?",
            "options": ["393", "938", "955", "300"],
            "answer": "955"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 857?",
            "options": ["849", "713", "42", "887"],
            "answer": "849"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 726?",
            "options": ["659", "718", "724", "575"],
            "answer": "718"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 598?",
            "options": ["617", "590", "658", "665"],
            "answer": "590"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 479?",
            "options": ["568", "471", "883", "712"],
            "answer": "471"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 86?",
            "options": ["78", "352", "289", "835"],
            "answer": "78"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 86?",
            "options": ["91", "110", "95", "78"],
            "answer": "78"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 393?",
            "options": ["448", "137", "385", "987"],
            "answer": "385"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 238?",
            "options": ["230", "970", "886", "831"],
            "answer": "230"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 969?",
            "options": ["385", "51", "263", "961"],
            "answer": "961"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 59?",
            "options": ["51", "730", "130", "727"],
            "answer": "51"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 756?",
            "options": ["8", "493", "623", "748"],
            "answer": "748"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 201?",
            "options": ["856", "193", "126", "735"],
            "answer": "193"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 977?",
            "options": ["969", "76", "686", "847"],
            "answer": "969"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 918?",
            "options": ["910", "352", "282", "158"],
            "answer": "910"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 997?",
            "options": ["392", "989", "946", "781"],
            "answer": "989"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 247?",
            "options": ["968", "281", "326", "239"],
            "answer": "239"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 416?",
            "options": ["408", "232", "322", "823"],
            "answer": "408"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 929?",
            "options": ["921", "448", "83", "861"],
            "answer": "921"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 249?",
            "options": ["83", "861", "327", "241"],
            "answer": "241"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 318?",
            "options": ["968", "137", "22", "310"],
            "answer": "310"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 289?",
            "options": ["392", "41", "281", "946"],
            "answer": "281"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 584?",
            "options": ["576", "721", "500", "293"],
            "answer": "576"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 801?",
            "options": ["754", "793", "637", "701"],
            "answer": "793"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 263?",
            "options": ["897", "373", "255", "111"],
            "answer": "255"
        },
    
        {
            "question": "8 less than 351?",
            "options": ["343", "629", "78", "518"],
            "answer": "343"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 529?",
            "options": ["240", "3", "521", "719"],
            "answer": "521"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 208?",
            "options": ["65", "876", "181", "200"],
            "answer": "200"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 657?",
            "options": ["859", "940", "649", "901"],
            "answer": "649"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 584?",
            "options": ["576", "622", "413", "918"],
            "answer": "576"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 472?",
            "options": ["292", "464", "149", "167"],
            "answer": "464"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 297?",
            "options": ["616", "923", "479", "289"],
            "answer": "289"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 408?",
            "options": ["443", "157", "451", "400"],
            "answer": "400"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 195?",
            "options": ["593", "187", "246", "121"],
            "answer": "187"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 550?",
            "options": ["542", "43", "349", "479"],
            "answer": "542"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 999?",
            "options": ["991", "212", "69", "647"],
            "answer": "991"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 714?",
            "options": ["89", "651", "246", "706"],
            "answer": "706"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 17?",
            "options": ["9", "803", "388", "845"],
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 872?",
            "options": ["864", "32", "535", "383"],
            "answer": "864"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 726?",
            "options": ["377", "177", "166", "718"],
            "answer": "718"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 461?",
            "options": ["641", "949", "934", "453"],
            "answer": "453"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 92?",
            "options": ["728", "962", "914", "84"],
            "answer": "84"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 919?",
            "options": ["785", "457", "911", "895"],
            "answer": "911"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 534?",
            "options": ["526", "757", "462", "815"],
            "answer": "526"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 104?",
            "options": ["96", "769", "437", "406"],
            "answer": "96"
        },
    
    {
            "question": "8 less than 741?",
            "options": ["330", "412", "733", "495"],
            "answer": "733"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 769?",
            "options": ["160", "290", "761", "323"],
            "answer": "761"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 678?",
            "options": ["670", "769", "425", "163"],
            "answer": "670"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 346?",
            "options": ["16", "338", "706", "378"],
            "answer": "338"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 667?",
            "options": ["633", "708", "659", "822"],
            "answer": "659"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 905?",
            "options": ["264", "893", "897", "958"],
            "answer": "897"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 183?",
            "options": ["175", "15", "230", "167"],
            "answer": "175"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 597?",
            "options": ["936", "188", "589", "391"],
            "answer": "589"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 329?",
            "options": ["642", "555", "731", "321"],
            "answer": "321"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 756?",
            "options": ["681", "748", "822", "335"],
            "answer": "748"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 634?",
            "options": ["249", "755", "626", "879"],
            "answer": "626"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 567?",
            "options": ["988", "780", "559", "53"],
            "answer": "559"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 511?",
            "options": ["503", "393", "261", "230"],
            "answer": "503"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 971?",
            "options": ["963", "96", "459", "191"],
            "answer": "963"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 less than 126?",
            "options": ["118", "906", "42", "727"],
            "answer": "118"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 725?",
            "options": ["716", "628", "886", "836"],
            "answer": "716"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 283?",
            "options": ["880", "147", "274", "318"],
            "answer": "274"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 17?",
            "options": ["808", "546", "8", "956"],
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 599?",
            "options": ["121", "590", "718", "231"],
            "answer": "590"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 342?",
            "options": ["115", "333", "603", "518"],
            "answer": "333"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 259?",
            "options": ["241", "250", "884", "695"],
            "answer": "250"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 996?",
            "options": ["507", "987", "884", "646"],
            "answer": "987"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 638?",
            "options": ["778", "629", "181", "231"],
            "answer": "629"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 789?",
            "options": ["780", "435", "476", "303"],
            "answer": "780"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 930?",
            "options": ["640", "921", "739", "381"],
            "answer": "921"
        },
    
        {
            "question": "9 less than 280?",
            "options": ["271", "633", "318", "D"],
            "answer": "271"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 381?",
            "options": ["372", "73", "357", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 333?",
            "options": ["457", "729", "324", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 834?",
            "options": ["825", "711", "561", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 631?",
            "options": ["622", "280", "690", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 972?",
            "options": ["329", "514", "83", "D"],
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 963?",
            "options": ["954", "240", "916", "135", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 436?",
            "options": ["184", "427", "614", "B"],
            "answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 250?",
            "options": ["241", "467", "692", "799", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 349?",
            "options": ["980", "181", "340", "871", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 793?",
            "options": ["273", "789", "165", "784", "D"],
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 349?",
            "options": ["600", "658", "53", "340", "D"],
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 872?",
            "options": ["257", "972", "863", "670", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 523?",
            "options": ["514", "173", "366", "215", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 125?",
            "options": ["116", "145", "482", "318", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 55?",
            "options": ["46", "771", "599", "967", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 640?",
            "options": ["88", "139", "631", "357", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 303?",
            "options": ["294", "416", "3", "876", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 75?",
            "options": ["721", "66", "674", "245", "B"],
            "answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 288?",
            "options": ["279", "962", "450", "502", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 733?",
            "options": ["724", "514", "12", "342", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 732?",
            "options": ["224", "777", "245", "723", "D"],
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 449?",
            "options": ["268", "823", "440", "175", "C"],
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 420?",
            "options": ["411", "626", "556", "862", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 less than 962?",
            "options": ["953", "665", "540", "119", "A"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
    
      {
        "question": "9 less than 232?",
        "options": ["223", "231", "151", "164"],
        "answer": "223"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 900?",
        "options": ["448", "539", "891", "798"],
        "answer": "891"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 560?",
        "options": ["360", "551", "34", "803"],
        "answer": "551"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 323?",
        "options": ["314", "328", "395", "15"],
        "answer": "314"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 563?",
        "options": ["396", "5", "454", "554"],
        "answer": "554"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 630?",
        "options": ["621", "955", "748", "5"],
        "answer": "621"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 246?",
        "options": ["283", "237", "698", "275"],
        "answer": "237"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 365?",
        "options": ["168", "50", "69", "356"],
        "answer": "356"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 550?",
        "options": ["541", "257", "420", "749"],
        "answer": "541"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 674?",
        "options": ["844", "213", "665", "615"],
        "answer": "665"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 949?",
        "options": ["184", "940", "555", "483"],
        "answer": "940"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 737?",
        "options": ["480", "129", "745", "728"],
        "answer": "728"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 720?",
        "options": ["711", "310", "674", "870"],
        "answer": "711"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 284?",
        "options": ["275", "432", "941", "591"],
        "answer": "275"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 802?",
        "options": ["680", "793", "792", "962"],
        "answer": "793"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 979?",
        "options": ["825", "450", "970", "214"],
        "answer": "970"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 944?",
        "options": ["971", "388", "935", "453"],
        "answer": "935"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 663?",
        "options": ["654", "978", "4", "815"],
        "answer": "654"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 121?",
        "options": ["91", "364", "221", "112"],
        "answer": "112"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 988?",
        "options": ["360", "979", "914", "317"],
        "answer": "979"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 203?",
        "options": ["539", "194", "181", "687"],
        "answer": "194"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 173?",
        "options": ["344", "161", "164", "258"],
        "answer": "164"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 699?",
        "options": ["657", "690", "756", "335"],
        "answer": "690"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 379?",
        "options": ["443", "12", "421", "370"],
        "answer": "370"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 72?",
        "options": ["63", "504", "147", "461"],
        "answer": "63"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "9 less than 991?",
        "options": ["982", "329", "69", "502"],
        "answer": "982"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 520?",
        "options": ["832", "714", "511", "474"],
        "answer": "511"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 313?",
        "options": ["840", "418", "397", "304"],
        "answer": "304"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 547?",
        "options": ["538", "161", "659", "257"],
        "answer": "538"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 166?",
        "options": ["888", "157", "5", "421"],
        "answer": "157"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 451?",
        "options": ["118", "442", "958", "223"],
        "answer": "442"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 447?",
        "options": ["438", "172", "756", "70"],
        "answer": "438"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 209?",
        "options": ["633", "200", "460", "389"],
        "answer": "200"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 813?",
        "options": ["72", "804", "385", "524"],
        "answer": "804"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 894?",
        "options": ["690", "885", "629", "647"],
        "answer": "885"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 676?",
        "options": ["496", "110", "667", "382"],
        "answer": "667"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 439?",
        "options": ["430", "744", "35", "944"],
        "answer": "430"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 156?",
        "options": ["754", "147", "555", "326"],
        "answer": "147"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 310?",
        "options": ["314", "651", "309", "301"],
        "answer": "301"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 206?",
        "options": ["153", "387", "14", "197"],
        "answer": "197"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 13?",
        "options": ["105", "4", "574", "439"],
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 929?",
        "options": ["918", "920", "964", "894"],
        "answer": "920"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 689?",
        "options": ["680", "912", "355", "231"],
        "answer": "680"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 380?",
        "options": ["88", "843", "371", "702"],
        "answer": "371"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 728?",
        "options": ["240", "719", "338", "390"],
        "answer": "719"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 45?",
        "options": ["395", "36", "478", "390"],
        "answer": "36"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 873?",
        "options": ["409", "602", "864", "436"],
        "answer": "864"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 586?",
        "options": ["896", "93", "421", "577"],
        "answer": "577"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 517?",
        "options": ["508", "467", "774", "775"],
        "answer": "508"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 39?",
        "options": ["691", "53", "30", "967"],
        "answer": "30"
      },
    
      {
        "question": "9 less than 218?",
        "options": ["209", "978", "35", "564"],
        "answer": "209"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 238?",
        "options": ["447", "405", "399", "229"],
        "answer": "229"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 211?",
        "options": ["865", "17", "927", "202"],
        "answer": "202"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 866?",
        "options": ["275", "349", "857", "823"],
        "answer": "857"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 131?",
        "options": ["122", "728", "809", "935"],
        "answer": "122"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 67?",
        "options": ["681", "58", "75", "461"],
        "answer": "58"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 496?",
        "options": ["940", "894", "983", "487"],
        "answer": "487"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 264?",
        "options": ["169", "124", "7", "255"],
        "answer": "255"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 466?",
        "options": ["561", "822", "167", "457"],
        "answer": "457"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 484?",
        "options": ["475", "258", "411", "620"],
        "answer": "475"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 947?",
        "options": ["682", "236", "938", "143"],
        "answer": "938"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 591?",
        "options": ["177", "582", "851", "5"],
        "answer": "582"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 231?",
        "options": ["440", "670", "454", "222"],
        "answer": "222"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 69?",
        "options": ["243", "60", "171", "507"],
        "answer": "60"
      },
      {
        "question": "9 less than 51?",
        "options": ["649", "100", "445", "42"],
        "answer": "42"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 824?",
        "options": ["814", "259", "989", "982"],
        "answer": "814"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 137?",
        "options": ["354", "979", "127", "926"],
        "answer": "127"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 568?",
        "options": ["354", "754", "558", "429"],
        "answer": "558"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 361?",
        "options": ["129", "351", "468", "15"],
        "answer": "351"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 986?",
        "options": ["976", "233", "27", "753"],
        "answer": "976"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 932?",
        "options": ["825", "922", "860", "279"],
        "answer": "922"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 803?",
        "options": ["98", "796", "793", "741"],
        "answer": "793"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 331?",
        "options": ["441", "980", "766", "321"],
        "answer": "321"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 261?",
        "options": ["4", "251", "260", "542"],
        "answer": "251"
      },
      {
        "question": "10 less than 605?",
        "options": ["595", "365", "109", "142"],
        "answer": "595"
      },
    
        {
            "question": "10 less than 705?",
            "options": ["695", "111", "245", "23"],
            "answer": "695"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 894?",
            "options": ["884", "573", "454", "191"],
            "answer": "884"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 241?",
            "options": ["231", "757", "962", "5"],
            "answer": "231"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 339?",
            "options": ["329", "185", "914", "143"],
            "answer": "329"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 87?",
            "options": ["978", "743", "77", "791"],
            "answer": "77"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 987?",
            "options": ["977", "272", "827", "159"],
            "answer": "977"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 203?",
            "options": ["642", "869", "671", "193"],
            "answer": "193"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 489?",
            "options": ["136", "479", "180", "631"],
            "answer": "479"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 352?",
            "options": ["342", "58", "892", "284"],
            "answer": "342"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 591?",
            "options": ["64", "581", "24", "236"],
            "answer": "581"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 267?",
            "options": ["257", "453", "314", "421"],
            "answer": "257"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 960?",
            "options": ["950", "401", "204", "701"],
            "answer": "950"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 434?",
            "options": ["424", "568", "539", "694"],
            "answer": "424"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 159?",
            "options": ["657", "985", "949", "149"],
            "answer": "149"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 367?",
            "options": ["280", "865", "357", "364"],
            "answer": "357"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 32?",
            "options": ["836", "22", "357", "303"],
            "answer": "22"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 203?",
            "options": ["876", "474", "204", "193"],
            "answer": "193"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 715?",
            "options": ["266", "705", "883", "615"],
            "answer": "705"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 513?",
            "options": ["292", "796", "503", "695"],
            "answer": "503"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 988?",
            "options": ["744", "434", "828", "978"],
            "answer": "978"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 948?",
            "options": ["162", "788", "938", "626"],
            "answer": "938"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 969?",
            "options": ["744", "162", "959", "844"],
            "answer": "959"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 608?",
            "options": ["872", "977", "598", "743"],
            "answer": "598"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 902?",
            "options": ["191", "854", "892", "327"],
            "answer": "892"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 323?",
            "options": ["313", "976", "178", "181"],
            "answer": "313"
        },
    
        {
            "question": "10 less than 796?",
            "options": ["872", "315", "786", "157"],
            "answer": "786"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 92?",
            "options": ["82", "106", "901", "198"],
            "answer": "82"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 306?",
            "options": ["632", "296", "819", "780"],
            "answer": "296"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 337?",
            "options": ["327", "968", "842", "924"],
            "answer": "327"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 462?",
            "options": ["452", "676", "910", "335"],
            "answer": "452"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 808?",
            "options": ["924", "60", "774", "798"],
            "answer": "798"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 915?",
            "options": ["593", "174", "569", "905"],
            "answer": "905"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 52?",
            "options": ["883", "42", "809", "667"],
            "answer": "42"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 600?",
            "options": ["570", "590", "539", "204"],
            "answer": "590"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 668?",
            "options": ["954", "324", "487", "658"],
            "answer": "658"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 820?",
            "options": ["112", "147", "357", "810"],
            "answer": "810"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 443?",
            "options": ["826", "433", "635", "308"],
            "answer": "433"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 697?",
            "options": ["809", "228", "687", "141"],
            "answer": "687"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 322?",
            "options": ["361", "734", "312", "79"],
            "answer": "312"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 55?",
            "options": ["675", "45", "83", "261"],
            "answer": "45"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 260?",
            "options": ["538", "490", "250", "219"],
            "answer": "250"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 392?",
            "options": ["92", "293", "158", "382"],
            "answer": "382"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 389?",
            "options": ["241", "561", "379", "863"],
            "answer": "379"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 860?",
            "options": ["850", "938", "67", "222"],
            "answer": "850"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 522?",
            "options": ["512", "464", "611", "475"],
            "answer": "512"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 341?",
            "options": ["600", "331", "204", "358"],
            "answer": "331"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 689?",
            "options": ["978", "679", "332", "422"],
            "answer": "679"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 538?",
            "options": ["611", "528", "316", "534"],
            "answer": "528"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 482?",
            "options": ["472", "891", "868", "182"],
            "answer": "472"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 less than 535?",
            "options": ["32", "525", "466", "4"],
            "answer": "525"
        },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 170?",
        "options": ["563", "726", "262", "160"],
        "answer": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 443?",
        "options": ["882", "643", "433", "814"],
        "answer": "433"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 756?",
        "options": ["816", "658", "746", "667"],
        "answer": "746"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 954?",
        "options": ["209", "944", "674", "353"],
        "answer": "944"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 707?",
        "options": ["697", "936", "583", "615"],
        "answer": "697"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 665?",
        "options": ["655", "323", "108", "413"],
        "answer": "655"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 648?",
        "options": ["638", "360", "545", "50"],
        "answer": "638"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 745?",
        "options": ["536", "186", "951", "735"],
        "answer": "735"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 240?",
        "options": ["298", "948", "326", "230"],
        "answer": "230"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 408?",
        "options": ["398", "58", "260", "263"],
        "answer": "398"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 965?",
        "options": ["955", "137", "293", "543"],
        "answer": "955"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 806?",
        "options": ["82", "658", "631", "796"],
        "answer": "796"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 84?",
        "options": ["537", "74", "946", "735"],
        "answer": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 425?",
        "options": ["415", "960", "113", "785"],
        "answer": "415"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 906?",
        "options": ["896", "104", "835", "67"],
        "answer": "896"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 783?",
        "options": ["54", "570", "874", "773"],
        "answer": "773"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 361?",
        "options": ["770", "351", "491", "330"],
        "answer": "351"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 466?",
        "options": ["160", "456", "393", "954"],
        "answer": "456"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 527?",
        "options": ["655", "119", "517", "103"],
        "answer": "517"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 192?",
        "options": ["224", "539", "664", "182"],
        "answer": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 988?",
        "options": ["978", "64", "809", "982"],
        "answer": "978"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 849?",
        "options": ["839", "929", "755", "599"],
        "answer": "839"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 792?",
        "options": ["782", "532", "806", "127"],
        "answer": "782"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 971?",
        "options": ["961", "624", "581", "558"],
        "answer": "961"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 321?",
        "options": ["460", "523", "311", "828"],
        "answer": "311"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 316?",
        "options": ["776", "306", "397", "359"],
        "answer": "306"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 91?",
        "options": ["889", "259", "81", "389"],
        "answer": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 71?",
        "options": ["928", "945", "839", "61"],
        "answer": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 342?",
        "options": ["424", "546", "332", "78"],
        "answer": "332"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 459?",
        "options": ["140", "449", "309", "630"],
        "answer": "449"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 918?",
        "options": ["905", "603", "908", "231"],
        "answer": "908"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 435?",
        "options": ["425", "176", "847", "343"],
        "answer": "425"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 463?",
        "options": ["429", "453", "669", "863"],
        "answer": "453"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 740?",
        "options": ["592", "674", "730", "87"],
        "answer": "730"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 354?",
        "options": ["781", "614", "344", "919"],
        "answer": "344"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 499?",
        "options": ["489", "506", "596", "135"],
        "answer": "489"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 28?",
        "options": ["811", "382", "18", "375"],
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 890?",
        "options": ["880", "142", "251", "86"],
        "answer": "880"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 688?",
        "options": ["497", "678", "90", "115"],
        "answer": "678"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 less than 767?",
        "options": ["251", "732", "757", "158"],
       "answer": "757"
    },
    
];

export default level8questions;